Student Association; Records ua804
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Student Association Records1921-1989
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. Student Association
ua804
5.3 cubic ft.
The Student Association Records contains records documenting the proceedings of the UAlbany Student Association from its inception in 1921 to 1989. This collection contains records that relate to the changing duties, functions, and governmental structure of the Student Association.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this record group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the Student Association.
Administrative History
The current Student Association was formed in 1921. Interest in forming a student government dates from 1914. At that time, President Milne rejected a student petition to form a student government commenting, "There is no place in this institution for the association and activities contemplated in this petition". President A.R. Brubacher(1915-1939) took a more favorable attitude toward student government. In response to a 1915 student petition, he instructed Professor Risley to form a committee to study the possibility of creating a student government. There appears to have been an attempt at forming a rudimentary student organization in January, 1916. As a result of Risley's study, Myskania was formed in 1917. Myskania, referred to in their 1917 constitution as the student council, was an honorary body consisting entirely of seniors who were to represent "the opinion and to improve the department of the student body." Myskania, in turn, created the Student Association in 1921. The general business of running student funded activities such as the yearbook and the student newspaper appears to have been the concern of the Student Assembly. The new Student Association appears to have carried on the responsibilities of the Student Assembly. (For a history of Myskania, see the Myskania finding aid.)
The Student Association's original purpose as stated in its 1921 constitution, was "the management of all matters of student interest not academic in nature." The Student Association controlled the legislative, financial and executive powers of the government, while Myskania acted as a single judicial branch and as guardian of school traditions. According to the 1921 constitution, the executive duties of the S.A. fell on the executive board made up of the president, the vice president, the secretary and the treasurer. The Executive Board's duty was to carry out the provisions of the Assembly and act as a court of appeals. By 1928, a new constitution for the Student Association changed the executive branch. Instead of the Executive Board, the executive branch was run by Student Council, different from the original student council (Myskania), which was made up of the president, the vice president, the secretary, and the presidents of the four classes. The new Student Council had broader duties than the Executive Board including: arranging the program for Student Association meetings, providing for the publication of the student directory, charter all boards, committees and associations by securing support from the Student Association through the budget and executing all legislation passed by the Student Association.
In the 1930's and 40's Student Association assemblies dealt with contemporary issues such as the presidential campaigns, the New Deal, and World War II. In 1949 the Student Association was involved in a project called CARE, an organization to help the children of the war. From the end of the 1960's the Student Association has placed increasing emphasis on student rights and equal opportunity. Minorities began to organize themselves and form groups including the Women's Liberation Front, Black Students Alliance and Lesbians for Freedom and the Student Association gave formal recognition to these new organizations. The trend continues to this day. At the same time the Student Association supported new programs such as the Equal Opportunity Program (EOP), developed in 1973.
While continuing to sponsor equal opportunity programs for all races and creeds, the Student Association has also, in more recent years, turned its attention to the environment (NYPIRG was recognized on campus in 1982), as well as supported such academic initiatives as the Frosh Reading Program. Long term issues include opposition to ROTC, during the 1960's and 70's for its support for the United States Government's Vietnam War policy, in the 1980's because ROTC discriminated against gay and lesbian candidates; reproductive rights and the establishment of a Birth Control Center on campus. The prominent development of the 1970's through 1990's was the Student Association s new power in academic affairs--one prominent example of that was their accessing the competence of teaching faculty. The results of their surveys were distributed in the ACT and SCATE Booklets.
Scope and Contents
The Student Association record, consist of meeting minutes, subject files, student publications, booklets, bills and committee files.
Includes minutes of the Student Association and Central Council, 1921-49, 1969-89; Cenral Council bills and resolutions, 1966-89; subject files, 1940-44, 1959-88, consisting of a budget, constitutions, ACT (teaching assessment) proposals, announcements and newsletters; and committee records, 1941-88.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Student Association and Central Council Minutes, 1921-29, 1932-41, 1943-49, 1966-68, 1970-74, 1975-77, 1978-86, 1987-1989
Series 2 - Central Council Bills, 1965/66-1988/89
Series 3 - Subject Files, 1940-44, 1958-88
Series 4 - Committee Files, 1949-75
Series 5 - Assessment of Courses and Teachers (ACT and SCATE booklets), 1974-76, 1987, 1991
All series are arranged alphabetically with the exception of Series 1 and Series 2, which are arranged chronologically.
Athletics and Sports; Student government--United States; Albany (N.Y.); Newsletters; Administrative records; Membership; Minutes; Programs (documents); Financial Records; Correspondences; Web Archives; University at Albany Foundation
- Meeting Minutes, 1970-1988; 1; 1.76 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The earliest minutes date from the formation of the Student Association in 1921. They document the Student Association's interest in establishing and maintaining school traditions (1920's and 30's), the Student Association 's concern with academic issues such as the establishment of the honor system. These documents give an overview of the management of the organization, and document the Student Association structural change.
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 1)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1974 October (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 2)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1975 April (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 3)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 4)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 5)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 6)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 7)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1977 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Folder 8)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 9)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 10)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 11)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 12)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 13)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 14)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 15)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 16)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 17)
  - Minutes-Central Council [1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 2 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 1)
  - Minutes-Central Council [2 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 2 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 2)
  - Minutes-Central Council, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 3)
  - Minutes-Central Council [1 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 2 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 4)
  - Minutes-Central Council [2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 2 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 5)
  - Minutes-Central Council [1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 2 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 6)
  - Minutes-Central Council [2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 2 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 7)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 1)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 2)
  - Student Association Central Council-Minutes, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Meeting Minutes), Item 3)
- Central Council Bills, 1965-1989; 2; 1.76 cubic ft.
  The Central Council Bills are complete for the period 1965-66 to 1988-89. This series contains bills passed by the Central Council which is the legislative body of the student government. The bill relate to appropriations, budgets, recognition of student organizations, resolutions relating to local, state, national and international issues, student government reorganizations. The bills dating from 1978-79 to 1988-89 are bound and indexed from 1978-79 through 1985-86
  - Bills-Central Council #7, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 1)
  - Bills-Cental Council #47-49, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 2)
  - Student Association Bills, Cental Council, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 3)
  - Bills-Central Council #45, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 4)
  - Bills-Central Council # 14,25,32,97,125,143, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 5)
  - Bills-Central Council #49,54,58-64,68,81,82,84, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 6)
  - Bills-Central Council 1 of 2, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 7)
  - Bills-Central Council 2 of 2, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 8)
  - Bills-Central Council 1 of 2, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 9)
  - Bills-Central Council 2 of 2, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 10)
  - Bills-Central Council 1 of 2, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 11)
  - Bills-Central Council 2 of 2, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 12)
  - Bills-Central Council, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 13)
  - Bills-Central Council 1 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 14)
  - Bills-Central Council 2 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 15)
  - Bills-Central Council, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 16)
  - Bills-Central Council, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 17)
  - Bills-Central Council #2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 18)
  - Student Association Bills, Cental Council, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 19)
  - Bills and Resolutions, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Folder 20)
  - Student Association Bills, Cental Council 1980-1981 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 21)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 22)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 23)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 1)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 2)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 3)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 4)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 1)
  - Student Association Bills, Central Council, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (2-Central Council Bills), Item 2)
- Committee Files, 1949/1977; 3; 1.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  The Committee Files 1949-75 contain bills and minutes, constitutions, government reorganization files, and ballots relating to the proposals and projects made by different committees to the Central Council. The committees include the Academic Affairs Commission, 1967-71, Athletic Advisory Board, 1970-71, Big 4 Committee, 1949-53, Constitutional Revisions Committee, 1965, 1969, Election Commission, 1973-75, and the Government Reorganization Committee, 1962-64. Examples of some projects are: the Frosh Reading Program, Assembly Bill number 4162 (1971-72) regarding the use of non-virgin paper on campus and the establishment of a Birth Control Center for students
  - Academic Affairs Commission, 1967-1971 (Box 1 (3-Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Athletic Advisory Board-SA Bills and Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Athletic Advisory Board-SA Bills and Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Big 4 Committee-Recommendations, 1949-1953 (Box 1 (3-Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Constitutional Revisions Committee, 1965; 1969 (Box 1 (3-Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Election Commission-Ballots, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (3-Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Governmental Reorganization Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 1 (3-Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Executive Commission University Senate, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - University Senate, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - University Senate, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - University Senate Bills and Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - University Senate Councils and Committees, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - University Senate-Senate Proper, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - University Senate-Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - University Senate-Bills and Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - University Senate-Reports and Executive Community, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - University Senate-Councils And Committees, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (3-Committee Files), Folder 10)
- Academic Affairs, 1948-1986; 4; 1.03 cubic ft.
  The Academic Affairs Records contain documents related to the administration and finances of the Student Association. Also included are records relating to student activity on campus and campaign materials for the election of Student Association Members.
  - Acedemic Affairs Commission Report to Central Council, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 1)
  - Student Council Committee Reports and Recommendations, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 2)
  - Athletic Advisory Board- Budget, Rules, 1967 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 3)
  - Airforce ROTC "Cross-Town" Agreement, 1968 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 4)
  - Budgets, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 5)
  - Budgets-Requests, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 6)
  - Budgets, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 7)
  - Announcements-Assorted, 1970-1980 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 8)
  - Bits and Pieces-A.S.A. Newsletter, 1970; 1974 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 9)
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers (ACT) Blank Questionairres, 1974-1975; 1983 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 10)
  - Ballots, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 11)
  - Budgets, 1948-1949 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 12)
  - Budgets, 1965-1969 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 13)
  - Accountants Report: Financial Statements and Supplementary, 1967 June 30 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 14)
  - Budget Committee Minutes, 1979 March 26; 1979 April 03 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 15)
  - Budgets, 1970 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 16)
  - Central Council-Parking Strike, Undated (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 17)
  - Committee Reports and Recommendations, 1951-1952 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 18)
  - Central Council-Student Tax Police, Nomination Form, Correspondence and Flyers, ca. 1970-1975 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 19)
  - Budgets-Summary, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 20)
  - Committee on University Government Governance-SUNY Binghamton, Buffalo, Albany, 1967-1969 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 21)
  - Committee Reports and Recommendations, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 22)
  - Central Council-Supreme Court Application, ca. 1965 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 23)
  - Composition Services - SA - Styles and Sizes, Undated (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 24)
  - Committee to Draft Campus Alchol Policy-Recommendation, 1969 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 25)
  - Consolidated laws and Regulations of Student Association, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 26)
  - Consolidated laws and Regulations of Student Association, 1976 May 11 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 27)
  - Constitution (Tenative) of the State College Student Association, 1945 May 15 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 28)
  - Constitution-Student Association "Board", ca. 1962 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 29)
  - Constitution, 1965 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 30)
  - Constitution, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 31)
  - Constitution, Undated (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 32)
  - Directories, 1970-1977 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 33)
  - Financial Policies (SA), Undated (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-Assorted, 1951; 1959; 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 35)
  - Faculty Student Association Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 36)
  - Financial Resolutions, 1943-1949 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 37)
  - Moving-Up Date Programs and Recommendations, ca. 1940-1960 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 38)
  - NYCT Leadership Conference, 1954 May 23 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 39)
  - Ebenezer Howard Project, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 40)
  - Financial Statements, 1974 June 30 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 41)
  - Flyers and Brochures-Assorted, ca. 1970-1986 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 42)
  - Forms-Assorted, ca. 1965-1977 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 43)
  - Government Reorganization Committee Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 44)
  - Government Revision Workshop, 1964 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 45)
  - From Letters to Faculty Members, 1952; 1970; 1972; 1976; 1985 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 46)
  - From Letters to Students and Their Parents, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 47)
  - Elections-Flyers, 1972-1978; 1984-1987 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 48)
  - "Groups"-Directory of Student and Other Groups Recognized by The Student Association of SUNYA, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 49)
  - Informer-Issues #1 and #2, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 50)
  - Living Area Affairs Commission-Rationale for Women's Hours, 1967 March 15 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 51)
  - Operating Expenses: Central Council, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 52)
  - Press Release-Concerning The Bill, Restoration of Carver Community Health Center Funding, 1973 October 5 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 53)
  - Procedures for Organizational Recognition, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 54)
  - Schedule for Letter Writing Campaign, Undated (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 55)
  - Off-Campus Student Co-Op, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 56)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1975 February 5; 1974 March 6 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 57)
  - Student Association Handbook-SUNY Plattsburgh, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 58)
  - Student Evaluation of Courses Teachers-Blank Questionnaires and Instructions, ca. 1968-1974 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 59)
  - Student Government Conference-Information, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1964 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 60)
  - Student Government Reorganization Workshop, 1964 November 21 (Box 1 (4-Academic Affairs), Folder 61)
- Assessment of Courses and Teachers, 1974-1991; 5; 0.17 cubic ft.
  The Student Association gained the permission of the Administration to publish surveys of courses and teachers which are available to the students so that they could make more informed decisions in choosing their courses. The collection is incomplete, and while the faculty evaluations from the 1970's appear to be comprehensive, those from the 1980's and 1990's only publish ratings of a few courses where the faculty has given permission to publish.
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers, 1974 April (Box 1 (5-Assessment of Courses and Teachers), Folder 1)
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers, 1974 April (Box 1 (5-Assessment of Courses and Teachers), Folder 2)
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers, 1975 April (Box 1 (5-Assessment of Courses and Teachers), Folder 3)
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers, 1976 April (Box 1 (5-Assessment of Courses and Teachers), Folder 4)
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers, 1976 April (Box 1 (5-Assessment of Courses and Teachers), Folder 5)
  - Student Course and Evaluation, 1987 (Box 1 (5-Assessment of Courses and Teachers), Folder 6)
  - Student Course and Teacher Evaluation, 1991 April (Box 1 (5-Assessment of Courses and Teachers), Folder 7)
- Subject Files, 1943-1988; 6
  Arranged alphabetically
  This series contains constitutions, budgets, ACT teaching assessment proposals, announcements and newsletters, Moving-up Day programs, and government reorganization papers. In some cases there is extensive information on proposals such as the ACT's and the Ebenezer Howard Project, 1970-71, an attempt to involve students in the problems of urban poverty. The subjects range from local to state wide concerns including other SUNY schools.
  - Academic Affairs Commission - Report to Central Council, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Accountants' Report: Financial statements and Supplementary, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Airforce ROTC "Cross Town" agreement, 1968 June 30 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Announcements, 1970-1980 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers: ACT blank questionnaires, 1974-1975; 1983 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Athletic Advisory Board: Budget and Rules, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Ballots, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Bits and Pieces, 1970; 1974 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Budgets, 1948-1949 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Budgets: Requests, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Budgets, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Budgets, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Budgets, 1965-1969 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Budgets: Summary, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Budgets, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Budget Committee Minutes, 1979 March 19; 1979 March 26; 1979 April 3 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Central Council: Parking Strike, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Central Council: Student Tax Policy, Nomination Form, Correspondence and Flyers, ca. 1970-1975 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)